James T. Cox Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 4. Published Plays, Musicals, and Screenplays (arranged by call number), 4; This series consists of 724 titles which may be searched in the following ways: The entire series may be browsed by selecting the following link: This series may also be searched on the. You may browse the collection by entering "James T. Cox" under a subject search or you may search for a specific title or author by selecting the Advanced Search option. To use this option most effectively you should enter the "James T. Cox Collection" in the first search box and select "Subject" for the search type. You may enter any additional terms or keywords in the subsequent search boxes. This will allow you to search within Series 4 of the James T. Cox Collection. I wonder if it is worth talking with John to see if we can remove that text all together from the finding aid.